yellowassistance.com 2011-11-10

# YellowAssistance.com - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

**Introduction**  
YellowAssistance.com is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable Web experience possible. Generally speaking, you can use YellowAssistance.com without giving us any information about yourself. When we do need your personal information to provide additional and/or optional services that you request, such as My Place, this policy describes how we collect and use your personal information. YellowAssistance.com respects your right to personal privacy, and we will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. Rest assured your information will not be sold to anyone one for any purpose. 

Part I: Information Collection

_General Overview_ _  
_  
For the most part, you will not need to provide any private, personally identifiable information to use YellowAssistance.com. unless you choose to register as a user. You may elect to Set Your Address so that our search can provide listings in distance order based on where you live instead of the Geo-center of a city of zip code.

In the course of normal operation, our algorithms do collect and process a large number of not personally identifiable, information such as traffic patterns, clickstream logs, IP addresses, browser type, browser language, and the date and time of your visits. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. This information is used primarily to operate our service, and at times, to develop and improve our services further. 

We do track and catalog the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use this tracking information to determine and continuously refine the relevancy of our search results as well as to analyze which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. This helps us continue to build a better search tool for you.

_Registration_

Some of our additional and/or optional services may require registering for an account. For such services, we may ask you for some personally identifiable information in order to create an account and to provide the service. If we require personally identifiable information for such services, it will primarily be used to identify and ensure you are the account holder. It may also be used to notify you about your account, available options, and other products and services made available by Yellow Assistance, its parent company and its subsidiaries. It will not be shared with 3rd party sites or used for any other purposes other than reasons that are not specifically listed on the site. 

_Cookies_

As you probably know, "cookies" are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit them. YellowAssistance.com uses cookies as the basis for a number of personalized and/or customized features. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis. Furthermore, you can reset your browser at any time to refuse or delete all cookies. However, some YellowAssistance.com features or services may not function properly without cookies. 

Part II: Information Security

YellowAssistance.com takes information security very seriously. We protect user information with a number of security and technology measures in order to prevent unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. Furthermore, we strictly limit access to your personally identifying information only to those employees on a strict need-to-know basis in order to operate, develop or improve our services. 

Part III: Third Party Sites

We offer links to other Web sites. Please note that third party sites may have privacy standards that differ from ours. We do not control the content on any third party site, and we encourage you to read the privacy policies on third party sites when you click on their links. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer and/or collect personally identifiable information. 

Part IV: Changes to this Privacy Policy

This policy is likely to evolve throughout time. Any changes or updates to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

Effective 1/1/06
